Dustin C. Davis

 ¶ Jenks, Oklahoma, United States ■ davisdustin328@gmail.com □ 8152108011 □ in/dustindavis02/ ■ https://www.justdustinthings.com

SUMMARY

Just like in Life, Dustin would rather take action & fail, rather than taking no action at all. Reliable, coordinated, and diverse professional in the tech field with over 2 years of experience across several languages. Having developed and maintained code bases for over 2 years, Dustin is eager to apply the knowledge gained to improve and execute elite code for any application. Strong Communicator, Well Organized, & Reliable.

EXPERIENCE

General Merchandise

Target

November 2021 - Present, Tulsa, OK

- Developed new merchandising and pricing strategies to increase store sales by 15%, gained 10 new customers in a 30-day period.
- Utilized collection and reporting of sales data to identify consumer trends and react quickly to drive sales, improved inventory management through utilization of forecasting formulas and analytics tools.
- Researched and monitored competitive activity and current industry trends to create merchandise plans and pricing strategies.
- Modified existing plans and strategies in response to data, market fluctuations, and customer feedback.

Shift Manager

Pei Wei Asian Diner

November 2018 - July 2021, Tulsa, OK

- Responsible for managing a team of over 10 employees while ensuring operations continued without fail.
- Increased customer satisfaction by over 45% during 2021 through the efficiency of our team's work.
- Improved the customer experience by providing efficient support across all forms of communication.
- Ensured the quality control of all products & items purchased by customers.
- Responsible for all cash transactions and verification of the days sales.

PROJECTS

AutoClicker

Personal • https://github.com/DustinDavis02/Autoclicker • September 2023 - Present

- Implemented a AutoClicker application in Python to automate mouse clicks with a wide range of customizable options.
- Reduced task time by 100% through automation.
- Utilized user interface design principles for the application and developed debugging tools to ensure accuracy and ease of use.
- Developed unit tests and documentation for the application.

Sky Runner

Holberton • https://github.com/DustinDavis02/HackSprint • May 2023 - May 2023

- Developed "Sky Runner", a 2D platformer game with a cloud theme using 2D game development engine Unity.
- Sky Runner navigated through a complex landscape of three levels, collecting fruits to boost their score while dodging hazards.
- Successfully designed a game that has multiple levels using C# and Visual Studio.

EDUCATION

Diploma of Full Stack Web Development

Holberton Tulsa • Tulsa, OK • 2024 • 3.5 GPA

SKILLS

Programming Languages, Front-End Development, TypeScript, Node.js, Back-End Web Development, Python (Programming Language), Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), MySQL, HTML